BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Correspondence, 1944-1977; 1
  - People, 1945-1973; 2
    - Chunn, Prentis, 1952-1953 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Chunn, Prentis, 1953 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Cliburn, Van, 1958-1959 (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - Cole, Grover C., 1950 (Box 105, Folder 32)
    - Collier, Shelby, 1948-1949 (Box 105, Folder 33)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1948-1948 (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1948 (Box 105, Folder 35)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1949 (Box 105, Folder 36)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1950 (Box 105, Folder 37)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1951 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1952 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1953 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1954 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1955 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1955-1956 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1956 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1957 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1958 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1959 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1960 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1961 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1962 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1963 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1964 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1965 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1966 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1967-1968 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1968-1969 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1970 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1971 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Collins, Carr P. (1 of 3), 1972 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Collins, Carr P. (2 of 3), 1972 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Collins, Carr P. (3 of 3), 1972 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1973 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Collins, Carr P., 1974-1977 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Connally, Tom, 1950-1951 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Conner, Arlene, 1950-1953 (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Copeland, A.R., 1973 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Craig, Coleman (The Baptist Review), 1965-1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Craig, W. Marshall, 1948 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Creed, Kate R. (Mrs. J.J. Creed), 1954-1957 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Creed, Kate R., 1967-1976 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Crew, Charles C.-Charles C. Crew’s Will, 1948 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Criswell, W.A., 1958 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Criswell, Dr. W.A., 1960-1964 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Cullen, H.R., 1948-1951 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Culp, Mary Reed, 1949 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Dana, Charles, 1960 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Daniel, Bill, 1948-1949 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Daniel, Price, 1948-1953 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Daniel, Price, 1955-1956 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Daniel, Price, 1956-1957 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Daniel, Price, 1957-1958 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Daniel, Price, 1958-1959 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Daniel, Price, 1959-1961 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Daniel, Price, 1961-1963 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Davidson, Whitfield, 1960 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Day, R.E., 1949 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - DeBeaufort, Jack M., 1959 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Devereaux, Chuck, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Edgar, J.W., 1950-1951 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Edwards, Robert B., 1954 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - Eidson, Melvin C., 1949-1950 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Elliott, Raymond Manuscript, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Evans, Nella T., 1951-1958 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Eytan, Walter, 1959 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Feezor, Dr. Forrest C., 1954-1955 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Feezor, Dr. Forrest C., 1955-1957 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Feezor, Dr. Forrest C., 1957-1958 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Feezor, Dr. Forrest C., 1958-1961 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Fleming, Bessie, 1963-1966 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Fleming, William, 1949-1950 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Fleming, William, 1956-1959 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Fleming, William, 1959-1960 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Fleming, William, 1960-1961 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Fleming, William, 1961-1962 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Folley, A.J. (Board Member), 1949-1951 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Folley, A.J., 1960-1962 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Dr. Freericks, 1951 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Gardner, T.C., 1952-1956 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Geren, Dr. Paul, 1955-1956 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Geren, Dr. Paul, 1957-1959 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Gilbert, Ruth, 1962-1977 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - (Goldthwaite) City of, 1960 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Gooch, W.T., 1957 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Gooch, W.T., 1958, 1960 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Graham, Billy, 1951 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Graham, Billy, 1954-1956 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Graham, Billy, 1954-1957 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Graham, Billy, 1962-1964 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Hall, Arthur J., 1948 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Hall, Lemuel, 1948-1950 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Hall, Lemuel, 1955-1957 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Hamm, Jack, 1953-1954 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Hamm, Jack, 1955-1957 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1948 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1949 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1950 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1951 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1952 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1953 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1954 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1955 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1956 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1957 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1958 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1959 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1960 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1961 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1962 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Hankamer, Earl C., 1963 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Hankamer, Earl, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Hankamer, Earl, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Hankamer, Earl, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Hankamer, Earl, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Hankamer, Earl, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Hankamer, Earl, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Hankamer, Earl, 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Hankamer, Earl, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Hargrove, H.H., 1960 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Haswell, Dr. Harold A., 1958-1959 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Hawkins, R.M., 1955-1957 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Hawkins, R.M., 1951-1957 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Hays, Harry, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Hayes, Harry, 1952 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Hayes, Harry, 1953 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Hayes, Harry, 1954 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Hayes, Harry, 1956 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Hayes, Harry H., 1960-1962 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Heald, Henry T., 1960 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Henson, William S., 1954 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Hingson, Dr. Robert, 1950-1951 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Holcomb, Luther and T.L., 1948-1949 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Holcomb, Luther and T.L., 1950 (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Holcomb, Luther and T.L., 1951 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Holcomb, Luther and T.L., 1952-1953 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Holcomb, Luther and T.L., 1954-1955 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Holcomb, Luther and T.L., 1956-1958 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1948-1949 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Howard, Willis E., 1948 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Howard, W.F., 1955-1956 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Hunt, Arch, 1955 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Hunt, Arch, 1956 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Hunt, Arch W., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Hunt, Arch, 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Hunt, Arch, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Hunt, Arch, 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Hunt, H.L., 1958-1959 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Hunt, H.L., 1960-1961 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Hunt, H.L., 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Hunt, H.L., 1970-1971 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Hunt, H.L., 1973-1977 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Huey, Ruth, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Hutcherson, E.S., 1948-1951 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Irving, George, 1948-1950 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Jackson, Horace, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - James, Dr. E.S., 1960-1961 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - James, Dr. E.S., 1961-1963 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Jeffrey, James, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Johnson, A.F., 1949-1950 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Johnson, Senator Lyndon, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Johnson, Senator Lyndon, 1952 (Box 113, Folder 21)
    - Johnson, Senator Lyndon, 1953 (Box 113, Folder 22)
    - Johnson, Senator Lyndon, 1954 (Box 113, Folder 23)
    - Johnson, Senator Lyndon, 1955 (Box 113, Folder 24)
    - Johnson, Senator Lyndon, 1957 (Box 113, Folder 25)
    - Johnson, Senator Lyndon, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 26)
    - Kokernot, Herbert Jr., 1950-1951 (Box 113, Folder 27)
    - Lang, Aldon S., 1953 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Lang, Aldon S., 1954 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Lang, Aldon S., 1955 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Lang, Aldon S., 1956 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Lang, Aldon S., 1957 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Lang, Dean Aldon, 1958 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Lang, Aldon S., 1959 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Lee, Robert G., 1954 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Logan, Ralph, 1950 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Martin, D.K. (1 of 4), 1943-1951 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Martin, D.K. (2 of 4), 1943-1951 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Martin, D.K. (3 of 4), 1943-1951 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Martin, D.K. (4 of 4), 1943-1951 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Martin, D.K., 1951 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Martin, D.K., 1952 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Martin, D.K., 1953 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Martin, D.K., 1954-1955 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Martin, D.K., 1955-1956 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Martin, D.K., 1956-1957 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Martin, D.K., 1957-1958 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Martin, D.K., 1958-1959 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Martin, D.K., 1959 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Mayse, Pat, 1948 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - McCall, Dean Abner, 1955-1956 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - McCall, Dean Abner, 1956-1957 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - McCall, Dean Abner, 1957-1958 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - McCall, Dean Abner, 1958 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - McCall, 1958-1960 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - McCall, Abner, 1960 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - McCall, Abner V., 1960-1961 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - McCall, Abner V., 1961-1963 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - McCall, Abner V., 1963-1964 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - McCall, Abner V., 1964 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - McCall, Abner V. (President) (1 of 2), 1967-1969, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - McCall, Abner V. (President) (2 of 2), 1967-1969, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - McCaulley, Fred A., 1953-1958 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - McKnight, Dr. Roy, 1958-1963 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - McLean, Marrs, 1948-1950 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - McLean, Marrs, 1952-1956 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - McLean, Mrs. Rena Marrs, 1950-1958 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - McMahan, Dr. George T., 1960 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - McMurrey, Jim, 1959 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Milam, R.E., 1949 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Miller, A.C., 1950 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Mitchell, Angus, 1948-1949 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Moody, Dan, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Moody, Dan, 1953-1958 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Moore, L.H., 1959 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Morgan, C.A.( 1 of 4), 1963-1974 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Morgan, C.A. (2 of 4), 1963-1974 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Morgan, C.A. (3 of 4), 1963-1974 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Morgan, C.A. (4 of 4), 1963-1974 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Morrison, Mrs. R.W., 1948-1949 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Nabors, W.C., 1960 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Neff, Pat M., 1951 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Newman, Guy D., 1960-1962 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Nutt, Hal, 1960 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Olson, Dean Stanley, 1953 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Olson, Dean Stanley, 1954-1955 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Olson, Dean Stanley, 1956 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Olson, Dean Stanley, 1957 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Olson, Dean Stanley, 1958 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Olson, Dean Stanley, 1959-1960 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Olson, Dean Stanley, 1961-1964 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Orr, Dr. J. Edwin, 1962 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Pakis, William R. (1 of 4), 1966-1976 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Pakis, William R. (2 of 4), 1966-1976 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Pakis, William R. (3 of 4), 1966-1976 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Pakis, William R. (4 of 4), 1966-1976 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Parks, Largent, 1952 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Parks, Largent, 1953 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Parks, Largent, 1954 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Parks, Largent, 1955 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Parks, Largent, 1956 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Parks, Largent, 1957 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Patterson, Bill, 1949 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Payne, Lawrence, 1951 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Penland, G.H., 1952-1954 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Penland, G.H., 1955-1956 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Penland, G.H., 1957-1958 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Perry, W.C., 1955-1956 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Perry, W.C., 1957 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Perry, W.C., 1958 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Perry, W.C., 1959-1960 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Perry, Mrs. Roscoe, 1949 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Pew, J. Howard, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Poage, W.R., 1948 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Rayzor, J. Newton, 1960-1961 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Robertson, James T., 1955 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Robertson, James T., 1956 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Robertson, James T., 1956-1957 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Robinson, R.J. (Jackie), 1960 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Rodenhauser, Paul C.-Grand Recorder, 1969-1970 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Roloff, Lester L., 1954-1956 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Royal, Kenneth, 1948 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Russell, Mrs. Lily, 1948-1957 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Russell, Mrs. Lily, 1957-1958 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Sanders, J.W., 1949 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - Schofield, J.R., 1963 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - Sells, Murray C., 1958 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - Sessions, T.J., 1963-1964 (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - Sheppard, John Ben, 1953-1957 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - Shivers, Governor Allan, 1950-1953 (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - Shivers, Governor Allan, 1954-1955 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - Shivers, Allan, 1956-1957 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Dean George, 1958-1959 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Tarwater, Tom, 1960-1977 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Archie, 1956 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Archie, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Archie, 1958 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Taylor, Archie, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Archie, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Wadley, J.K., 1949-1950 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Washburn, Harry, 1956 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Washington, Harry, 1957, 1962-1974 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Watson, Murray, 1961-1963 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Weeks, C.E. (J, Edgar Hoover), 1948 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Well, Stone (Red), 1948-1950 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - White, Mrs. W.R., 1960-1967 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - White, Mrs. W.R., 1969-1970 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Whitson, Bobbie Carol, 1959 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Willers, Jack, 1960-1961 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Ben H., 1952-1953 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Ben H., 1954 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Ben H., 1955-1957 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Gene, 1972-1973 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Williams, J. Howard, 1948-1956 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Wimpee, Dr. W.J.-Hong Kong Trip, 1960-1961 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Wimpee, W.J., 1960-1961 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Woodruff, Bob, 1949 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Wooten, Ben, 1950-1964 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Wunneburger, Louis, 1948-1949 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Yates, Kyle M., 1952-1953 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Yates, Kyle M., 1953 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Yates, Kyle M., 1955-1956 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Yates, Kyle M., 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Zimmerman (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Zimmerman (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Affiliations and Associations, 1946-1977; 3
    - Airways Club, 1962-1968 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - ALCOA Foundation, 1961 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - American Association of School Administrators, 1950 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1948-1950 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - American Association of University Women, 1950-1951 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - American Association of University Women, February 11, Houston, 1960-1961 February (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - American Council on Education, 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - American Ideals Conference, 1962 Fall (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Anti-Crime Council-Committee of 100, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting (1 of 5), 1967-1975 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting (2 of 5), 1967-1975 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting (3 of 5), 1967-1975 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting (4 of 5), 1967-1975 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting (5 of 5), 1967-1975 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting (1 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Association of Southern Baptist for Scouting (2 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - The Argyle, 1955-1956 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - The Argyle, 1955-1956 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Association of Texas Colleges, 1949-1950 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Bankers Life Company, 1967-1970 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Baptist Annuity Board, 1967-1973 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Baptist Brotherhood, 1948-1951 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Baptist Churches (1 of 3), 1969-1974 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Baptist Churches (2 of 3), 1969-1974 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Baptist Churches (3 of 3), 1969-1974 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Baptist Foundation, 1952 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Baptist Foundation, 1953 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Baptist Foundation, 1954-1956 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Baptist Foundation, 1956 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Baptist Foundation, 1960-1961 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas (1 of 4), 1948-1951 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas (2 of 4), 1948-1951 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas (3 of 4), 1948-1951 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas (4 of 4), 1948-1951 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1946 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Baptist General Convention, 1953 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1955 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1959-1960 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Baptist Standard, 1948 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Baptist Standard 1, 1957 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Baptist Standard 2 (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Baptist Standard 2 (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Baptist Student Union, 1960-1961 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Beer Election Campaign, 1956 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Better Fishing, Inc. (1 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Better Fishing, Inc. (2 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Bishop College (1 of 4), 1948-1951 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Bishop College (2 of 4), 1948-1951 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Bishop College (3 of 4), 1948-1951 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Bishop College (4 of 4), 1948-1951 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Bishop College, 1953 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Bishop College, 1955-1956 (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - Bishop College (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - Bishop College (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - Bishop College (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - Bishop College (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Bishop College (1 of 2), 1957-1959 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Bishop College (2 of 2), 1957-1959 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Boy Scouts-Heart O’ Texas Council (1 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Boy Scouts-Heart O’ Texas Council (2 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Boy Scouts (1 of 4), 1952 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Boy Scouts (2 of 4), 1952 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Boy Scouts (3 of 4), 1952 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Boy Scouts (4 of 4), 1952 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Boy Scouts-Meeting, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Boy Scouts of America (1 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Boy Scouts of America (2 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Boy Scouts of America (3 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Boy Scouts of America (4 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Boy Scouts of America (5 of 5), 1960-1961 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Boy Scouts Committee, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Boy Scouts of America 1, 1966-1977 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Boy Scouts of America 2, 1966-1977 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Boy Scouts-Heart O’ Texas Council 1, 1967-1977 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Boy Scouts-Heart O’ Texas Council 2, 1967-1977 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Buckner’s Orphan Home, 1949-1951 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Carnation Company, 1959-1961 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1959-1960 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1963-1964 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Christian Children’s Fund, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Christian Heritage Foundation, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Christian Life Commission, 1951 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Christian Life Commission, 1967-1975 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Christmas Greetings, 1951 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Citizen’s Committee for Hoover Report (1 of 3), 1949-1951 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Citizen’s Committee for Hoover Report (2 of 3), 1949-1951 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Citizen’s Committee for Hoover Report (3 of 3), 1949-1951 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Commerce, Texas East Texas State College, 1960 November 22-23 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Commissions-Mixed, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Companies and Corporations Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Conference on American Ideals, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Contributions and Dues, 1951 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Crusades Against Delinquency, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Current Legislation, 1953 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Daily Times Herald-Dallas, 1948 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1948 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Defense Training Mobilization, 1950-1951 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Democracy at Work, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Distinguished Service Awards, 1949-1950 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - The Elite Book Club of America, 1948 (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Esso Education Foundation, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - First Waco Corporation, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - Ford Foundation, 1951 (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - Ford Foundation, 1955-1956 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Mission Board, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - Foundations, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - Foundation for Religious Action, 1954-1956 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Foundations Mixed, 1960-1961 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Foundations Mixed, 1961-1962 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Foundation for Religious Action, 1956-1957 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Freedom in Action, 1961-1962 (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - Freedoms Foundation, Inc. (1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - Freedoms Foundation, Inc. (2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Freedoms Foundation, 1966-1968 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - George Washington on Gambling, undated (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 3), 1963-1976 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 3), 1963-1976 (Box 127, Folder 5)